rentacenter.com 2015-06-07

# Privacy Policy

|   
---  
  
|   
---  
  
We’ve located your nearest store.

Not your store?

Change  
  
| 

|   
---  
  
|   
---  
  
Rent-A-Center, Inc. (the "Company") is committed to the responsible handling of customer information. Because we gather certain types of information about online users, we want to help you understand our policies regarding the collection and use of that information. We updated our online privacy policy effective September 13, 2013. If you have any questions regarding the updated policy, please use the information provided below to contact our Customer Service Department. Below you will find answers to several questions regarding the Company's online privacy policy:  
  
 **1\. What information does the Company collect about you on this Web site and what does it do with the information?**  
The Company collects personally-identifiable information that you provide on one of our many on-line forms. These forms include a preliminary rental order, sweepstakes registration, online specials or contact requests, and online surveys. The personally-identifiable information ("personal information" or "your information") collected on this Web site can include some or all of the following - your name, address, phone number, email address, birthday, social security number, and information regarding your lease or mortgage and product interests.

In addition to the personal information identified above, the Company also automatically receives and records data from our servers and from your browser when you visit this Web site, including your IP address, the time, and information about the page you requested and the Web site through which you were linked to our site, if any. We may use tracking technologies in a variety of ways, including the following: keeping count of return visits to our site; accumulating and reporting anonymous, aggregate (data collected in mass), statistical information on Web site usage; and determining which features users like best. If you do not want us to collect this information from your browser for these purposes, you can tell us that by "

[opting out](https://metrics.rentacenter.com/optout.html?locale=en_US&popup=true "Opt Out")".

Finally, your Internet browser has a feature called "cookies," which stores small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to our site. Cookies tell us nothing about who you are, however, unless you specifically give us personal information. You do not need to have cookies turned on to visit rentacenter.com. You may also elect not to allow cookies to be collected by selecting certain options on your browser.

We use your personal information gathered on this Web site for a variety of purposes, including targeting specific customers for special offers. The data we collect is used to facilitate the processing of rental orders and to give us demographic information about our audience. We use this data to understand that audience and to improve our offerings to you, our customer. In addition, the personal information you provide allows us to inform you of additional special offers that may be forthcoming, send you coupons, or notify you of products and services of our affiliates that relate directly to your specific interests, hobbies or other information you have given.

 **2\. With whom does the Company share the information?**  
The Company may share the personal information gathered on this Web site in limited circumstances. For example, the Company may release the information to third parties providing services on the Company's behalf, such as advertising and marketing the Company's products and services, or to reputable third-party affiliates to provide you with valuable information or special offers. The Company may disclose the information to third parties in connection with a court order, subpoena, government investigation, or when otherwise required by law. The Company may report to law-enforcement authorities conduct it believes may be unlawful, and may release to such authorities personal information relating to such suspected unlawful conduct. The Company may release some or all personal information if necessary to protect the Company's rights or property or to protect the safety of the Company's employees or others. Personal information may also be released to third parties in the event of a corporate sale, merger, acquisition, or similar event.

Rent-A-Center, Inc. is the parent company of Rent-A-Center East, Inc., Rent-A-Center West, Inc., and Rent-A-Center Texas, L.P. Accordingly, all information gathered about you by the Company may be shared with any of the Company's current or future subsidiaries or affiliates.

Your information will not be disclosed by the Company except as discussed in this Privacy Policy.

 **3\. How do I correct or update my personal information?**  
You can correct or update information previously submitted to the Company by visiting your local Rent-A-Center store and providing Rent-A-Center with the updated information. In addition, you can choose not to receive further electronic communications from us. To do this, simply follow the URL provided at the end of each electronic communication you receive on our behalf and request the deactivation of your information from the Company's database.

 **4\. How does the Company protect the security of my personal information?**  
The Company will use appropriate security measures to protect your information in a secure, controlled environment. The Company has made substantial investments in server, database, backup, and firewall technologies to protect the security and integrity of your information. In the event that a security breach does occur and your information is acquired by an unauthorized person, we will take appropriate steps to contain the breach and to notify you of the unauthorized acquisition.

 **5\. Does the Company's Web site link to other websites?**  
Yes. This Web site provides links to other Web sites that are not owned or operated by the Company. Such Web sites are not subject to the Company's Privacy Policy. Accordingly, you should consult the privacy policies of those Web sites, if any, prior to entering any personal information on those Web sites.

 **6\. What is the effective date of the Company's Privacy Policy and how will the Company notify me of changes to its Privacy Policy?**  
This Privacy Policy is effective September 13, 2013. Any material changes to this Privacy Policy will be posted on this Web site.

 **7\. How does the Company handle children's privacy online?**  
The Company's Web site is intended for a general audience. The Company does not knowingly collect personal information about children or enter into rental-purchase transactions with children. In accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, the Company does not permit registration by, and will not knowingly collect or use personal information from, anyone under 13 years of age. If the Company is notified that it has inadvertently collected personal information from anyone under 13 years old, it will destroy such information. If you are under the age of 18, you must ask a parent or legal guardian to order merchandise from the Company.

 **8\. How do I contact the Company?**  
Click here for information on how to contact our Customer Service Department with questions or comments.  
  
| 

| Stay connected with Rent-A-Center and keep up with our latest deals, tips and news!  
---  
  
|   
  
---  
© 2015 Rent-A-Center® All Rights Reserved. | Privacy Policy | Web Accessibility | ePay Terms | California Transparency in Supply Chain Act  
  
Transaction is a rental-purchase agreement (or in NV, a lease agreement with an option to purchase; in IA, ND, NE, and SC, a consumer rental-purchase agreement; in CT and NH, a rent-to-own agreement; in AK, DC, DE, HI, ID, KS, OR, SD, VA, and WA, a lease-purchase agreement; in MA and RI, a lease; or in VT a consumer lease agreement). Not available in MN or WI. You will not own the merchandise until the total amount necessary to acquire ownership is paid in full or you exercise your early purchase option ("EPO"). Ownership is optional. MA and RI consumers: at any time after the initial payment, you may purchase the merchandise for 80% of the remaining Total Number of Payments, plus sales tax, calculated at the time. In VT, minimum 18-week rental period applies. 90 days same as cash not available in VT. Product availability and pricing may vary by store. Participating locations only.

 ***Sharp 60" AQUOS HD LED Smart TV (LC60LE660U) and Any 32" TV Bundle:** $29.99 a week for 127 weeks, Total of All Payments: $3,808.73, GA Cost of Lease Services: $1,808.75; WV- $29.99 a week for 118 weeks, Total of All Payments: $3,538.82, Retail/Cash Price: $1,489.12, Rent-to-own Charge: $2,049.70; CA- $29.99 a week for 121 weeks, Total of All Payments: $3,628.79; ME- $29.99 a week for 124 weeks, Total of All Payments: $3,718.76; HI- $29.99 a week for 124 weeks, Total of All Payments: $3,718.76. **Acer Aspire 15.6" HD Widescreen Notebook Computer (ES1-512-C5WE) and Select Tablets Bundle (LG G Pad 10.1" Tablet LGV700AUSARD):** $24.99 a week for 79 weeks, Total of All Payments: $1,974.21, GA Cost of Lease Services: $1,006.48   
; WV- $24.99 a week for 74 weeks, Total of All Payments: $1,849.26, Retail/Cash Price: $782.66 , Rent-to-own Charge: $1,066.60; CA- $24.99 a week for 73 weeks, Total of All Payments: $1,824.27; ME- $24.99 a week for 75 weeks, Total of All Payments: $1,874.25; HI- $24.99 a week for 75 weeks, Total of All Payments: $1,874.25; PA- $24.99 a week for 79 weeks, Total of All Payments: $1,974.21, Cost of Lease Services: $986.71. **Acer Aspire Z1 19.5" HD+ All-in-One Computer (AZ1-611-UR51) and Select Tablets Bundle (LG G Pad 10.1" Tablet LGV700AUSARD):** $24.99 a week for 89 weeks, Total of All Payments: $2,224.11, GA Cost of Lease Services: $1,056.38; WV- $24.99 a week for 85 weeks, Total of All Payments: $2,124.15, Retail/Cash Price: $948.15 , Rent-to-own Charge: $1,176.00; CA- $24.99 a week for 84 weeks, Total of All Payments: $2,099.16; ME- $24.99 a week for 87 weeks, Total of All Payments: $2,174.13   
; HI- $24.99 a week for 87 weeks, Total of All Payments: $2,174.13; PA- $24.99 a week for 89 weeks, Total of All Payments: $2,224.11, Cost of Lease Services: $1,056.37. Samsung Galaxy S5 (GS5BLKNPS1) and Select Tablets Bundle (Samsung Galaxy Note 8.0 Tablet GALAXY8BUN): $29.99 a week for 112 weeks, Total of All Payments: $3,358.88, GA Cost of Lease Services: $1,962.14; WV- $29.99 a week for 100 weeks, Total of All Payments: $2,999.00, Retail/Cash Price: $1,310.96 , Rent-to-own Charge: $1,688.04; ME- $29.99 a week for 100 weeks, Total of All Payments: $2,999.00; HI- $29.99 a week for 100 weeks, Total of All Payments: $2,999.00; PA- $29.99 a week for 112 weeks, Total of All Payments: $3,358.88, Cost of Lease Services: $1,842.13. Offer good while supplies last and cannot be combined with any other promotion. The "Total Price" does not include applicable taxes, optional fees, and other charges (such as late charges) that you may incur. Advertised rental rates and terms are for new merchandise only. Prices not valid outside U.S. Reduced weekly rates will not reduce early purchase option or total amount necessary to acquire ownership. Advertised rates begin 6/1/15 and end 6/20/15. Bundle offers reduce weekly rates when compared to weekly rates for renting bundled items separately. Bundle offers will not reduce total amount necessary to acquire ownership or purchase-option amounts. Only select items may be bundled; some items excluded. "Save up to $10 per week" claim based on non-promotional weekly rates and applies only to 60" Sharp LED SMART TV (LC60LE66OU) combined with 32" TV (32LB520B). "Save $7 per week" claim based on non-promotional weekly rates and applies only to Samsung Galaxy S6 (GS5BLKNPS1) combined with select tablets (GALAXY8BUN). "Save up to $18 per week" claim based on non-promotional weekly rates and applies only to Acer 15" Laptop (ES1-512) combined with Select Tablets (LGV700AUSARD) and Acer 18.5" All-In-One computer (AZ1-611-UR51) combined with Select Tablets (LGV700AUSARD).

^Smartphones starting at $14.99 per week" refers to a new agreement for one **Samsung Galaxy S3 (GS3WHTNPS1):** $14.99 a week for 65 weeks, Total of All Payments: $974.35, GA Cost of Lease Services: $525.35; WV- $14.99 a week for 65 weeks, Total of All Payments: $974.35, Retail/Cash Price: $449.00 , Rent-to-own Charge: $525.35; PA- $14.99 a week for 65 weeks, Total of All Payments: $974.35, Cost of Lease Services: $475.35.

See Store Manager for complete details. Consulta con el Gerente de la Tienda para los detalles completos.

**Pre-approved means no credit check and no credit needed. Agreement requires verification of residence, income and four personal references. Delivery and set-up are included, and RAC services and maintains the merchandise while on rent or in NJ, for duration stated on agreement; set-up does not include connection of gas appliances. For model upgrades, simply return the product you are currently renting and open a new agreement for another model. You can return your product and freeze your payments. To restart an agreement on a returned product, Rent-A-Center will retain your payment records for two years. Thereafter, simply bring in your last payment receipt for reinstatement. In VT, minimum 18-week rental period applies. 90 days same as cash not available in VT.

All other trademarks, registered trademarks and/or service marks, indicated or otherwise, are the properties of their respective owners. Samsung, Galaxy Note, Galaxy S, S Pen, Super AMOLED, Multi Window, and The Next Big Thing Is Here are all registered trademarks of Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. Android, Google, Google Maps are a trademark of Google Inc. Use of this trademark is subject to [Google Permissions](http://www.google.com/permissions/). Acer, the Acer logo and Aspire are registered trademarks of Acer Inc. Other trademarks, registered trademarks and/or service marks, indicated or otherwise, are the properties of their respective owners.
